Anything else you want? We still have half a day.
هل تريد أي شيء آخر؟ لا يزال لدينا نصف يوم.
No, it's okay. I've already gotten more than enough.
لا، لا بأس. لقد حصلت على ما يكفي.
Come on!
تعال!
Well...
حسنًا...
Hmm... How about a real sushi bar, not one of those conveyor belt places?
ممم... ماذا عن بار السوشي الحقيقي، وليس أحد تلك الأماكن ذات الحزام الناقل؟
Or maybe a designer watch?
أو ربما ساعة مصممة؟
Hmm...
همم...
Then...
ثم...
A kiss.
قبلة.
I want a kiss.
أريد قبلة.
Whoa, that's a bit...
واو، هذا قليلا...
But you're the one who said I could ask for anything.
لكنك أنت من قال أنني أستطيع أن أطلب أي شيء.
- Well, yeah, but... - A man should be true to his word, right?
- حسنًا، نعم، ولكن... - يجب على الرجل أن يكون صادقًا في كلمته، أليس كذلك؟
That's not the same thing.
هذا ليس نفس الشيء.
Hey, are you trying to run away again?
مهلا، هل تحاول الهروب مرة أخرى؟
- Are you okay? - Y-Yeah.
- هل أنت بخير؟ - نعم.
In that case, go out with me.
في هذه الحالة، اخرج معي.
Hey, Hi-ro!
مرحبا، مرحبا!
Simmered sea bream. Isn't it amazing? I've been filleting fish since this morning.
سمك الدنيس المطهو على نار هادئة. أليس رائعًا؟ لقد بدأتُ بتقطيع السمك منذ الصباح.
- Let's eat.
- دعنا نأكل.
Now I remember.
الآن أتذكر.
A long time ago, someone taught me how to read kanji.
منذ وقت طويل، علمني شخص ما كيفية قراءة الكانجي.
Because of that, I actually started to study a little.
وبسبب ذلك، بدأت فعليا بالدراسة قليلا.
Thanks to that person, I didn't have to repeat a year and was able to get a job.
بفضل هذا الشخص، لم أضطر إلى إعادة عام واحد وتمكنت من الحصول على وظيفة.
I'll definitely make you fall for me.
سأجعلك تقع في حبي بالتأكيد.
Ah, ah, ah...!
آه، آه، آه...!
Hah! Ahhh!
هاه! آه!
Whoa! Gotcha!
واو! فهمت!
Ahhh! Nice. A good stretch.
آه! جميل. امتداد جيد.
Hah. Shall we go?
هاه. هل نذهب؟
- Date resumes. - What?
- تاريخ السيرة الذاتية. - ماذا؟
Say cheese.
قل الجبن.
It feels nice.
إنه شعور جميل.
To be celebrated properly like this.
ليتم الاحتفال به بشكل صحيح مثل هذا.
Thanks, Hiro.
شكرا لك هيرو.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
You're the one who requested it, Natsuo.
أنت من طلب ذلك، ناتسو.
I know, but...
أنا أعلم، ولكن...
What?
ماذا؟
I want to do it again.
أريد أن أفعل ذلك مرة أخرى.
Again?
مرة أخرى؟
You said my birthday still has half a day left.
لقد قلت أن عيد ميلادي لا يزال لديه نصف يوم متبقي.
I did, but what did you mean by do it again...
لقد فعلت ذلك، ولكن ماذا تقصد بفعل ذلك مرة أخرى...
How about a hug?
ماذا عن العناق؟
Huh?
هاه؟
I can do a hug.
أنا أستطيع أن أعانق.
Hiro...!
هيرو...!
This isn't a dream...!
هذا ليس حلما...!
Thank you very much.
شكراً جزيلاً.
Ahh! I was so nervous dyeing a customer's hair by myself for the first time.
آه! كنت متوترة جدًا وأنا أصبغ شعر زبونة بنفسي لأول مرة.
But the client seemed really happy, so I'm glad.
لكن العميل بدا سعيدًا حقًا، لذا أنا سعيد.
W-W-Was I... bad?
WW-هل كنت... سيئًا؟
Oh. N-No, not at all.
أوه. لا، على الإطلاق.
You were... amazing.
لقد كنت... مذهلاً.
- Oh... - Amazing.
- أوه... - مدهش.
Oh, what a relief.
أوه، ما هذا الإرتياح.
Man, I was really nervous. My hands were shaking when I was mixing the dye.
يا رجل، كنت متوترًا جدًا. كانت يداي ترتجفان أثناء خلط الصبغة.
Hiro-kun! I know I'm a little early, but I'm here.
هيرو-كن! أعلم أنني مبكر قليلاً، لكنني هنا.
- Welcome. - Here's a little something for you.
- مرحبًا بك. - إليك شيئًا صغيرًا لك.
- Oh, it's just you, Tsuboi-san... - Huh?
- أوه، أنت فقط، تسوبوي سان... - هاه؟
Oh, no. I mean, no, no, no, no!
أوه، لا. أعني، لا، لا، لا، لا!
I-I mean, thank you so, so much for coming.
أعني، شكرا جزيلا لك على حضورك.
- Asahi, show her to her seat. - Oh, right.
- أساهي، أريها مقعدها. - أوه، صحيح.
- Okay, this way please. - Wait, did he just say...?
- حسنًا، من هنا من فضلك. - انتظر، هل قال للتو...؟
- This way. Oh! You must've misheard. - Misheard?
- من هنا. أوه! لا بد أنك سمعتَ خطأً. - هل سمعتَ خطأً؟
- Yep. - Really?
- نعم. - حقا؟
Yes. You misheard.
نعم لقد أخطأت في السمع.
I didn't hear a thing. This way, this way.
لم أسمع شيئًا. من هنا، من هنا.
- Welcome. - Come in, come in.
- أهلاً وسهلاً. - تفضل بالدخول، تفضل بالدخول.
Huh?
هاه؟
Seriously, how many times have you looked at it?
بجدية، كم مرة نظرت إليه؟
You've checked your phone at least ten times today.
لقد قمت بفحص هاتفك عشر مرات على الأقل اليوم.
Waiting for someone?
في انتظار شخص ما؟
I'm not waiting for anyone.
أنا لا أنتظر أحدا.
Who in the world would I be waiting for?
من في العالم سأنتظر؟
"The Proper Way to Write Love"
"الطريقة الصحيحة لكتابة الحب"
Someone s waiting for me.
هناك شخص ينتظرني.
(Episode 5: How to Deal with a Love Rival (Traumatic ))
(الحلقة 5: كيفية التعامل مع منافس الحب (صدمة))
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Me?
أنا؟
- What are you looking at? - You're in the way.
- ماذا تنظر إليه؟ - أنت في الطريق.
- Why are you here? - Are you here to confess your love?
- لماذا أنت هنا؟ - هل أنت هنا للاعتراف بحبك؟
Okay, the Button Prince's love confession is about to begin!
حسنًا، اعتراف الأمير بالحب على وشك أن يبدأ!
- Say it! C'mon. - Hahaha.
- قلها! هيا. - هاهاها.
Button Prince, a few words for us, please! Go!
يا أمير الأزرار، بضع كلمات لنا من فضلك! انطلق!
Totally me...
أنا تماما...
Um...
واحد...
Welcome.
مرحباً.
- Is this your first time here? - Yes.
- هل هذه هي المرة الأولى لك هنا؟ - نعم.
So, what are we doing today?
إذن ماذا نفعل اليوم؟
Um... I would like you to make me look good.
اممم... أريدك أن تجعلني أبدو بمظهر جيد.
Look good...
تبدو جيدة...
- You have a date, maybe? - Oh, no, no.
- هل لديك موعد، ربما؟ - أوه، لا، لا.
I was thinking of going to see someone I used to have a thing with.
كنت أفكر في الذهاب لرؤية شخص اعتدت أن أتعامل معه.
Oh, I see. How exciting.
أوه، أرى. كم هو مثير.
- I think that person was... - Huh?
- أعتقد أن هذا الشخص كان... - هاه؟
I think that person might have been in love with me.
أعتقد أن هذا الشخص قد يكون يحبني.
- Is that so? - Hey, Hiro!
- هل هذا صحيح؟ - مهلا، هيرو!
- Natsuo! - Washizawa!
- ناتسو! - واشيزاوا!
No way, Oribe? Is that you, Oribe?
مستحيل يا أوريبي؟ هل هذا أنت يا أوريبي؟
I knew it was you, Washizawa!
لقد عرفت أنه أنت، واشيزاوا!
Wow. Running into you here... It feels like fate!
واو. صادفتك هنا... كأنه قدر!
What are you even doing here?
ماذا تفعل هنا؟
- It's been like four years, man. - Yeah. I was in the neighborhood...
- مرت أربع سنوات يا رجل. - أجل. كنت في الحي...
- and was just about to contact you. - Me?
- وكان على وشك الاتصال بك. - أنا؟
Seriously? Man, that makes me so happy.
بجد؟ يا رجل، هذا يجعلني سعيدًا جدًا.
That's my line.
هذا هو خطي.
Um...
واحد...
Oh, this is Oribe Mamoru.
أوه، هذا أوريبي مامورو.
An old coworker from a part-time job.
زميل عمل قديم من وظيفة بدوام جزئي.
And this is Hiro. And, uh...
وهذا هيرو. و، آه...
- I'm Shiina. - Oh, right, Shiina-chan.
- أنا شيينا. - أوه، صحيح، شيينا-تشان.
- By the way, Hiro's my personal hair artist. - Personal?
- بالمناسبة، هيرو هو فنان شعري الشخصي. - شخصي؟
- Yep. - I'm just his regular stylist.
- نعم. - أنا مجرد مصفف شعره المعتاد.
- Huh? - Oh, is that all? Good.
- هاه؟ - أوه، هذا كل شيء؟ جيد.
- Hmm?
- همم؟
Oh, uh... It's nothing.
أوه، اه... لا شيء.
- Right this way, Mr. Oribe. - Thank you.
- من هنا، السيد أوريبي. - شكرا لك.
- I'll take your bags for you. - Oh, thanks.
- سآخذ حقائبك لك. - أوه، شكرا لك.
Who was that guy?
من كان هذا الرجل؟
Like I said, an old coworker.
كما قلت، زميل قديم في العمل.
What kind of work?
أي نوع من العمل؟
A convenience store. Did I never mention it?
متجر صغير. ألم أذكره قط؟
The company I worked at before closed down,
لقد أغلقت الشركة التي كنت أعمل بها من قبل،
so I was working there to make ends meet.
لذلك كنت أعمل هناك لتغطية نفقاتي.
Huh.
هاه.
You had a crush on him.
لقد كنت معجبة به.
How did you know?
كيف عرفت؟
I could just tell.
لا أستطيع إلا أن أقول.
What's this? Are you jealous, Hiro-kun?
ما هذا؟ هل أنت غيور يا هيرو-كن؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
It was completely one-sided on my part.
لقد كان الأمر من جانب واحد تمامًا من جانبي.
Is he really your type?
هل هو حقا نوعك المفضل؟
What if he is?
ماذا لو كان كذلك؟
- Weirdo. - Heh.
- غريب. - هاه.
So blunt.
صريحة جداً.
Whatever. I'm gonna go grab a drink with him.
لا يهم. سأذهب لشرب مشروب معه.
It's been four years, after all.
لقد مرت أربع سنوات، بعد كل شيء.
- Aren't you going to get a wash first? - Nah, I'm good.
- ألن تغتسل أولاً؟ - لا، أنا بخير.
I just came to see your face, Hiro.
لقد جئت فقط لرؤية وجهك، هيرو.
Besides...
بجانب...
I've been dying to see you since then.
لقد كنت متشوقًا لرؤيتك منذ ذلك الحين.
Is it just me?
هل أنا فقط؟
Hey, Hiro. You can head out for the day. You've been working so much overtime lately.
أهلاً هيرو، يمكنك الخروج اليوم. لقد عملت ساعات إضافية كثيرة مؤخرًا.
- What? Seriously? - I'll take over.
- ماذا؟ بجد؟ - سأتولى الأمر.
- Thanks so much. - See you.
- شكرا جزيلا. - أراك لاحقا.
- Good work today. - See you tomorrow.
- عمل جيد اليوم. - أراك غدا.
Oh... This is...
أوه... هذا...
Geez.
يا إلهي.
Natsuo... Natsuo...
ناتسو...ناتسو...
- Hehe. It looks good on you. - Where's Natsuo?
- ههه. يبدو رائعًا عليك. - أين ناتسو؟
Oh...
أوه...
Huh? You think so?
هاه؟ هل تعتقد ذلك؟
Yeah, it looks great.
نعم، يبدو رائعا.
- This is actually pretty nice. - Right? It's so cute.
- هذا جميل جدًا. - صحيح؟ إنه لطيف جدًا.
- Edamame. - Do you wear green a lot?
- ادامامي. - هل ترتدي اللون الأخضر كثيرًا؟
Yeah.
نعم.
- Oh, really? - I guess I do. Yeah.
- أوه، حقًا؟ - أعتقد ذلك. نعم.
Oh... Natsuo!
أوه... ناتسو!
- Really? Hey, with this one, we can match. - Natsuo!
- حقًا؟ مهلاً، بهذه، يُمكننا التطابق. - ناتسو!
Oh... you're right.
أوه... أنت على حق.
Natsuo.
ناتسو.
Oh, my bad.
أوه، خطئي.
Geez. Here.
يا إلهي، هنا.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Oh, hi. We met earlier.
مرحباً، لقد التقينا سابقاً.
Oh, right. Hi.
اوه، صحيح. مرحبًا.
Um... do you two keep in touch outside of work?
اممم... هل تتواصلان مع بعضكما خارج العمل؟
Uhh...
اه...
- Actually, Hiro's my boyf... - No, um, we're neighbors.
- في الواقع، هيرو هو صديقي... - لا، نحن جيران.
We grab a bite to eat sometimes. Right?
أحيانًا نتناول لقمةً. أليس كذلك؟
- Yeah. - So you're just meal buddies?
- نعم. - إذن أنتم مجرد أصدقاء للوجبة؟
Uh, yeah.
أوه نعم.
- Are you holding up okay? - Huh?
- هل أنت صامد بشكل جيد؟ - هاه؟
See? He's such a handful, isn't he?
أرأيت؟ إنه صعب المراس، أليس كذلك؟
And that T-shirt. If you don't like it, you really shouldn't get it.
وهذا القميص. إن لم يعجبك، فلا يجب عليك شراؤه.
He forced you into getting a matching one, didn't he?
لقد أجبرك على الحصول على واحدة مطابقة، أليس كذلك؟
- Hey! - Hit the nail on the head, didn't I?
- مهلا! - لقد ضربت على المسمار على رأسه، أليس كذلك؟
No.
لا.
He didn't force me.
لم يجبرني.
I'm the one who wants to get matching shirts with Washizawa.
أنا الشخص الذي يريد الحصول على قمصان متطابقة مع Washizawa.
Oribe...
أوريبي...
Alright! I say the three of us go grab some food.
حسناً! أقول أن نذهب نحن الثلاثة لتناول بعض الطعام.
What do you say? It's on me.
ماذا تقول؟ إنه عليّ.
- Oh, um, I... - Don't force him to go.
- أوه، أممم، أنا... - لا تجبره على الذهاب.
- Huh? - Can't you see you're making him uncomfortable?
- هاه؟ - ألا ترى أنك تجعله يشعر بعدم الارتياح؟
- That's not it. - Oh, my bad.
- ليس هذا هو الأمر. - أوه، خطئي.
It's just that...
إنه فقط ذلك...
I want it to be just the two of us.
أريد أن نكون فقط اثنين.
If we're going to eat,
إذا كنا سنأكل،
just me and Washizawa...
فقط أنا وواشيزاوا...
Then I'll leave you two to it.
ثم سأترككما لذلك.
Huh? Oh...
هاه؟ أوه...
H-Hiro...
هـ-هيرو...
What's with that guy?
ماذا حدث مع هذا الرجل؟
Who says something like that?
من يقول شيئا كهذا؟
And seriously, wasn't it great of me to read the room?
وبجدية، أليس من الرائع مني أن أقرأ الغرفة؟
What's with that weird T-shirt anyway?
ما الأمر مع هذا القميص الغريب على أي حال؟
This one is way cooler.
هذه الطريقة أكثر برودة.
For crying out loud.
من أجل الصراخ بصوت عال.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Hiro, what was that all about back there?
هيرو، ما الذي كان يدور في ذهنك هناك؟
- What are you talking about? - Oribe was worried about you.
- ماذا تتحدث عنه؟ - كان أوريبي قلقًا عليك.
- Your attitude, Hiro. - Is this about Oribe again?
- موقفك، هيرو. - هل هذا يتعلق بأوريبي مرة أخرى؟
- What? - It's just...
- ماذا؟ - إنه فقط...
- Are you two done already? - Yeah.
- هل انتهيتما بالفعل؟ - نعم.
It seems like things aren't going too well for him at work.
يبدو أن الأمور لا تسير على ما يرام بالنسبة له في العمل.
Oh, really?
أوه حقًا؟
He's pretty down about it,
إنه محبط جدًا بشأن هذا الأمر،
and the fact that he came to see me means he must be going through a lot.
وحقيقة أنه جاء لرؤيتي تعني أنه لابد وأن يمر بالكثير.
Hmm...
همم...
Actually, something like this has happened before.
في الواقع، لقد حدث شيء مثل هذا من قبل.
Though I'm sure it's different from last time.
على الرغم من أنني متأكد من أنها مختلفة عن المرة الأخيرة.
Last time?
آخر مرة؟
Something like this happened before?
هل حدث شيء مثل هذا من قبل؟
Yeah... uh, no, it's nothing.
نعم... أوه، لا، إنه لا شيء.
Natsuo, don't get too involved.
ناتسو، لا تتدخل كثيرًا.
There's only so much you can do, even as a friend.
هناك الكثير مما يمكنك فعله، حتى كصديق.
I know, but...
أنا أعلم، ولكن...
He's weak, unlike you, Hiro.
إنه ضعيف، على عكسك، هيرو.
What?
ماذا؟
You're talented and strong, Hiro. But he's...
أنت موهوب وقوي يا هيرو. لكنه...
What's that supposed to mean?
ماذا يعني ذلك من المفترض؟
If that's what you think,
إذا كان هذا ما تعتقد،
then why did I lose the last competition?
إذن لماذا خسرت المسابقة الأخيرة؟
That's not what I mean.
هذا ليس ما أقصده.
Then what do you mean? What are you...
إذن ماذا تقصد؟ ماذا أنت...
Besides, it's pathetic.
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، إنه أمر مثير للشفقة.
Running to the guy who used to have a crush on you just because things get tough.
الركض إلى الرجل الذي كان معجبًا بك فقط لأن الأمور أصبحت صعبة.
How could you say that?
كيف يمكنك أن تقول ذلك؟
That's why I told you two to stop licking each other's wounds!
لهذا السبب قلت لكما أن تتوقفا عن لعق جروح بعضكما البعض!
Geez...
يا إلهي...
Seriously, Hiro, what's with you?
بجدية، هيرو، ما الأمر معك؟
Why are you so mad?
لماذا انت غاضبة هكذا؟
There was no need to get that angry.
لم يكن هناك داعي للغضب .
Maybe Hiro wanted to come get dinner with us too?
ربما أراد هيرو أن يأتي لتناول العشاء معنا أيضًا؟
Then... he should've just said so.
إذن... كان ينبغي عليه أن يقول ذلك.
Well, I'm heading out for the day.
حسنًا، أنا ذاهب للخروج لهذا اليوم.
Oh! Hiro-kun, see you tomorrow.
أوه! هيرو-كون، أراك غدًا.
Maybe I'll go grab a drink somewhere.
ربما سأذهب لشرب مشروب في مكان ما.
Wow! Such a beautiful color.
واو! لون جميل جدًا.
So it's time for the Schobertii to bloom.
لقد حان الوقت الآن لتزدهر نباتات شوبيرتي.
Oh, this one's cute, too.
أوه، هذا لطيف أيضًا.
Thank you very much.
شكراً جزيلاً.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I couldn't help it! We made eye contact!
لم أستطع منع نفسي! تواصلنا بالعين!
- So, you think it'll work out with him? - Yeah.
- إذن، هل تعتقد أن الأمر سينجح معه؟ - نعم.
But you haven't actually spoken to him yet, right?
ولكنك لم تتحدث معه فعليا بعد، أليس كذلك؟
Well, that's where I'm counting on you, senpai.
حسنًا، هذا هو المكان الذي أعتمد عليك فيه، سينباي.
You're unbelievable.
أنت لا تصدق.
Nah, he's a total pushover. It'll be a piece of cake.
لا، إنه شخص سهل المنال. سيكون الأمر سهلاً.
Like yesterday, I bought a weird T-shirt near here...
مثل أمس، اشتريت قميصًا غريبًا بالقرب من هنا...
and he was overjoyed just by that.
وكان في غاية السعادة من ذلك.
- He's got a crush on you, right? - Yeah. A pretty serious one.
- إنه معجب بكِ، صحيح؟ - أجل. معجبٌ جدًا.
Plus, this is the second time! Most people would be suspicious by now, right?
هذه هي المرة الثانية! معظم الناس الآن سيشكّون، أليس كذلك؟
- The second time? What an idiot. - Heh heh...
- المرة الثانية؟ يا له من أحمق. - ههه ههه...
Who are you calling an idiot?
من تناديه أحمق؟
- Oh... - What are you talking about?
- أوه... - ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
Are you Mr. Washizawa?
هل أنت السيد واشيزاوا؟
Ah, yes. I'm with this organization.
أه نعم. أنا مع هذه المنظمة.
This is a pyramid scheme.
هذا مخطط هرمي.
No, no, no. It's not like that at all.
لا، لا، لا. الأمر ليس كذلك على الإطلاق.
We're a company founded on a solid philosophy...
نحن شركة تأسست على فلسفة راسخة...
Wait, this isn't him. This isn't Washizawa.
انتظر، هذا ليس هو. هذا ليس واشيزاوا.
You approached Natsuo just to rope him into this?
هل اقتربت من ناتسو فقط لتوريطه في هذا الأمر؟
So what if I did?
فماذا لو فعلت ذلك؟
What's it to you?
ما الأمر بالنسبة لك؟
It's his own fault for falling for it.
إنه خطؤه لأنه وقع في هذا الفخ.
It's the second time! He's just an idiot!
هذه المرة الثانية! إنه مجرد أحمق!
- What?! - Hey...
- ماذا؟! - مهلا...
Don't tell me you two are actually dating?
لا تخبرني أنكما تتواعدان فعلاً؟
It looks like he's not doing so well at work.
يبدو أنه ليس على ما يرام في العمل.
Is this about Oribe again?
هل يتعلق الأمر بأوريبي مرة أخرى؟
- What? - Oh, uh, nothing.
- ماذا؟ - أوه، لا شيء.
He's feeling pretty down about it,
إنه يشعر بالإحباط بسبب هذا الأمر،
and the fact that he came to see me means he must be going through a lot.
وحقيقة أنه جاء لرؤيتي تعني أنه لابد وأن يمر بالكثير.
I say the three of us go get dinner. Come on.
أقول أن نذهب نحن الثلاثة لتناول العشاء. هيا.
What do you say? It's on me.
ماذا تقول؟ إنه عليّ.
Look, don't worry. It was completely one-sided on my part.
لا تقلق، لقد كان الأمر من طرف واحد تمامًا.
I'm gonna go grab a drink with him. It's been four years, after all.
سأذهب لأشرب معه. لقد مرّت أربع سنوات، على كل حال.
Actually, something like this has happened before.
في الواقع، لقد حدث شيء مثل هذا من قبل.
Though I'm sure it's different from last time.
على الرغم من أنني متأكد من أنها مختلفة عن المرة الأخيرة.
Me? Seriously? Man, that makes me so happy.
أنا؟ بجد؟ يا رجل، هذا يسعدني جدًا.
He's weak, unlike you, Hiro.
إنه ضعيف، على عكسك، هيرو.
You're talented and strong, Hiro. But he's...
أنت موهوب وقوي يا هيرو. لكنه...
This is the second time! Most people would be suspicious by now, right?
هذه هي المرة الثانية! معظم الناس سيشكّون الآن، أليس كذلك؟
The second time? What an idiot.
المرة الثانية؟ يا له من أحمق!
But he's...
لكن هو...
That's just pathetic.
إنه أمر مؤسف للغاية.
How could you play with Natsuo's feelings like that?
كيف يمكنك اللعب بمشاعر ناتسو بهذه الطريقة؟
Hey!
يا!
- Hiro, stop it! - Natsuo!
- هيرو، توقف! - ناتسو!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
- Hey, are you okay, Oribe? - Why don't you ask him?
- أهلاً، هل أنت بخير، أوريبي؟ - لماذا لا تسأله؟
Actually, never mind. Don't ask.
في الواقع، لا بأس. لا تسأل.
And you better not say a word either.
ومن الأفضل لك أيضًا عدم قول كلمة واحدة.
Right...
يمين...
Hiro.
هيرو.
Open up.
إفتح.
It's raining.
إنها تمطر.
Here.
هنا.
I'm sorry. I didn't know anything...
أنا آسف. لم أكن أعرف شيئًا.
I'm sorry you had to do that for my sake.
أنا آسف لأنك اضطررت إلى القيام بذلك من أجلي.
All because I was too blind to see it.
كل هذا لأنني كنت أعمى جدًا بحيث لم أتمكن من رؤيته.
- All because I was so stupid, you had to... - It's not your fault.
- كل هذا لأنني كنت غبيًا جدًا، كان عليك أن... - ليس خطأك.
You believed in him, right?
لقد آمنت به، أليس كذلك؟
That's why you fell for it... twice.
لهذا السبب وقعت في الفخ... مرتين.
He's the one who betrayed you.
إنه هو الذي خانك.
So it's not your fault, Natsuo.
إذن هذا ليس خطؤك، ناتسو.
Hiro...!
هيرو...!
But you need to value yourself more.
ولكن عليك أن تقدر نفسك أكثر.
Stop putting yourself down all the time.
توقف عن التقليل من شأن نفسك طوال الوقت.
Listen, you are not someone who deserves to be used like that.
اسمع، أنت لست شخصًا يستحق أن يتم استخدامه بهذه الطريقة.
Understand?
يفهم؟
Yeah.
نعم.
- Hey. - Hmm?
- مهلا. - همم؟
What did you see in a guy like that?
ماذا رأيت في رجل مثل هذا؟
Oh... he reminds me of someone.
أوه... إنه يذكرني بشخص ما.
My first love.
حبي الأول.
- Your first love? - Yeah.
-حبك الأول؟ -نعم.
Back in high school, when I couldn't even read kanji...
في المدرسة الثانوية، عندما لم أكن أستطيع حتى قراءة الكانجي...
Remember I told you about the guy who'd write out the readings for me?
هل تتذكر أنني أخبرتك عن الرجل الذي كان يكتب القراءات لي؟
Our messy school courtyard...
ساحة مدرستنا الفوضوية...
and how there was this sweet guy who took care of it every single day.
وكيف كان هناك هذا الرجل اللطيف الذي اعتنى بها كل يوم.
You mean...
هل تقصد...
Suzuki Hiromu.
سوزوكي هيرومو.
Come to think of it, his name is almost the same as Hiro's.
إذا فكرت في الأمر، اسمه هو تقريبا نفس اسم هيرو.
And the way he loves gardening... They're so alike...
وكيف يحب البستنة... إنهم متشابهون جدًا...
Wait...
انتظر...
Don't tell me... Hiro is Suzuki Hiromu?
لا تخبرني... هيرو هو سوزوكي هيرومو؟
(Next Episode: The way to hide wounds (emotions)) - Ow! - Hiro-kun?
(الحلقة القادمة: طريقة إخفاء الجروح (العواطف)) - أوه! - هيرو-كون؟
- No, no, it's fine. Just sit down, Hiro. - But...
- لا، لا، لا بأس. اجلس يا هيرو. - لكن...
Hiro. Here you go. Open up.
هيرو، تفضل، افتح.
This is the line. Don't you dare cross it, you hear me?
هذا هو الحد. لا تجرؤ على تجاوزه، هل تسمعني؟
What happened to you? It's like you're in love.
ماذا حدث لك؟ كأنك في حالة حب.
That must be nice.
يجب أن يكون هذا لطيفا.
Having someone waiting for you.
أن يكون هناك شخص في انتظارك.
- I don't get it! If I don't like it, I don't like it! - Hiro!
- ما فهمت! إذا ما عجبني، ما عجبني! - هيرو!